<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Muhammad Amir Iqbal</title><link>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Muhammad Amir Iqbal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2023</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adapting Learning Classifier System for Image Classification</title><link>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/blog/image-classification-paper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/blog/image-classification-paper/</guid><description>Image classification is one of the most important and much explored problem in machine learning. Evolutionary computation techniques have been applied for image classification for a lesser degree. Even where it is applied to images, it is almost always applied to features pre-extracted from images and not directly at the pixel level. This makes the decision about the kind of features to be extracted a manual one. This paper presents a novel approach for image classification using Learning Classifier Systems that does not require manually designed features.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am a person who loves engaging with people to appreciate different perspectives and to keep learning and enjoying. I highly value originality, humbleness and honesty. I am blessed with a supportive wife and three amazing girls. I enjoy reding books, cycling and weight-lifting.
I have twenty-five years of ICT industry experience working in multicultural environments in Pakistan, Singapore, and Oman. Most of my professional life is spent on managing teams and projects, interacting with clients and vendors and delivering results.</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mamiriqbal1.github.io/cv/</guid><description>Experience# Project Manager 2022-07 - 2023-08 Educative — Educative Accelerates Developer Productivity Lahore, Pakistan Task and people management for a team of software engineers working as technical content developers
Introduced process and metrics for measuring the quality of the content and reviews. Assistant Professor 2018-08 - 2022-06 National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences — Computer Science Department Lahore, Pakistan Teaching courses in the Software Engineering and Data Science streams</description></item></channel></rss>